BACK IN THE '80s AND '90s,INFORMATION WAS KEY.
BUT NOW IT'S A WHOLE NEW GAME.
THESE DAYS,WITH THE INTERNET,
TWO FRESH GRADS SITTING INSOME SHIT WINDOWLESS BOX
MIGHT BEPUSHING AROUND MORE MONEY
THAN SOMEOF THE BIGGEST FUNDS,
AND GETTING INFORMATIONFASTER THAN ANYONE ELSE
BECAUSE THEY'REMASTERS OF A CHAT ROOM.
THAT'S WHY OUR JOBIS NOT JUST ABOUT INFORMATION;
IT'S ABOUT INTELLIGENCE.
WHEN WE BUY A STOCK,
IT'S BECAUSEAN IDIOT SOLD IT TO US.
AND WHEN I SAY US,
I DON'T MEAN THOSE PUSSIESOVER ON WALL STREET.
HEDGE FUNDS, GENTLEMEN,ARE THE FUTURE.
AND WE THRIVE NOT ONLY BY OURABILITY TO DECIPHER THE CLUES,
AND READ BETWEEN THE LINES,BUT BY DESIGNING FOOLPROOF PLANS
TO BE EXECUTED TO THE 'T'BY SUPERCAPITALISTS.
WE ARE A SUPERIOR,COVERT AGENCY OF OPERATIVES
CREATED AND INCENTIVIZEDTO FULFILL ONE MISSION:
YOUR GOD GIVEN RIGHT
TO MAKE AS MUCH MONEY AS YOU CANBEFORE YOU DIE.
WE WILL BEAR ARMSWITH OUR WORDS,
AND MORE IMPORTANTLY...
GO TO WAR IF NEED BE,USING ALL TACTICS,
IMAGINABLE...AND UNIMAGINABLE.
BECAUSE WE CREATE EVENTS--
EVENTS TO UNLOCKSHAREHOLDER VALUE.
AND THAT'S WHY OUR FUNDIS UP 25% YEAR OVER YEAR
FOR THE LAST FIVE YEARS.
WHAT ABOUT ASIA?
WE GOT A GUYSET UP IN HONG KONG.
REAL SMART.KNOWS HIS STUFF.
( indistinct chatter )
PLAYBOY,YOU'RE TAKING A LONG TIMETO ROLL THEM DICE, MAN!
Man: COME ON, BABY!COME ON, BABY! COME ON!
COME ON, MAN, SHIT!
( all yelling )
♪ THROW IT OUT, Y'ALL ♪
♪ THROW, THROW, THROW,THROW IT OUT, Y'ALL, Y'ALL ♪
♪ THROW IT OUT, Y'ALL,CASH IN THE CLIP ♪
♪ THROW IT OUT, Y'ALL,THROW IT OUT, Y'ALL, Y'ALL ♪
Man: AW!
THAT'S BULLSHIT!
♪ THROW IT OUT, Y'ALL ♪
♪ THROW IT OUT,CASH IN THE CLIP ♪
♪ BIG HOUSE ON THE HILL ♪
♪ GOT THE BIG HOUSEON THE HILL ♪
Man: TRADERS ARE ON EDGEAT THE MOMENT AS THEY AWAIT
FOR THAT FEDERAL RESERVEANNOUNCEMENT ON INTEREST RATES.
RAISING RATES SUBSTANTIALLY,
WELL, COULD HAVEA DRAMATIC EFFECT
ON THE U.S. ECONOMY;
IT COULD CHOKE OFF GROWTH,
AS HIGHER BORROWING COSTSMEAN THAT PEOPLE
FIND IT HARDERTO TAKE OUT LOANS.
EXPERTS ARE WARNING, THOUGH,THAT THERE IS A NEED
FOR HIGHER BORROWING COSTSTO CURB INFLATION.
( laughs ) ONE PERCENT,RIGHT, CONNER? SURE!
GUESS WORD GOT OUT--YOU REALLY THINK FED'SGOING TO CUT RATES TO 1%?
THIS IS THE ONE, ANDY.I CAN FEEL IT.
THAT'S WHAT I LIKEABOUT YOU MAN, CRAZY!
YO, CONNER, MAN, THANKS AGAINFOR THOSE ANALYTICS YESTERDAY,SPOT ON!
HEY, REMEMBER, BOX SEATS!
SERIOUSLY WITH THIS GUY.HEY LET ME ASK YOU SOMETHING.
WHAT'S UP?THIS FRIDAY...
YANKEES VERSUS METS?WHAT YOU GOT, MAN?
JOHNSON VERSUS KISHITA?YES, SIR.
I HEARD WORD ON THE STREETIS THAT KISHITA BROKE UPWITH HIS FIANCéE,
SO, HE'S GOING TO BEA LITTLE DISTRACTED.HOW DO YOU KNOW THAT?
COME ON! YANKEES BY TWO.JUST GO WITH ME ON THIS.
OKAY, THAT'S WHATI'M TALKING ABOUT.
( indistinct chatter )
BIG DAY TODAY.
YOU READY?
YEAH.
Woman: MR. BROWN, YOU ARECONFERENCE CONNECTED.
Mark:WHAT HAVE YOU GOT FOR ME?
HENDRICKS?
OLD MAN KAFFI OVER AT R.A.W.
IS ABOUT TO KICK THE BUCKET,SO WE'RE GOING TO SHORT.
OUCH. PRETTY BOY?
WE'RE EXPECTING THE FEDTO ANNOUNCE BIG NUMBERS,
SO WE'RE JUST GOINGTO SIT TIGHT TODAY.
PUSSIES!
OKAY, ONE MORE THINGON THE AGENDA TODAY, GUYS--
WE'RE GOING TO SAY SAYONARATO HONG KONG, EVERYBODY,
IT'S TIME TO DUMPFEI &amp; CHANG.
( sounds of annoyance )
OKAY, EVERYBODY, IF THAT'S IT...
HEY, MARK. IT'S CONNER.
LOOK, BASED ON MY ANALYSISOF WHAT'S GONNA HAPPEN TODAY,
I THINK WE SHOULD ACTUALLYINCREASE OUR POSITIONON FEI &amp; CHANG.
Mark:TO HOW MUCH?
EIGHTY OR NINETY MILLION.
HAVE YOU COMPLETELYLOST YOUR MIND?
LOOK FED'S IN A BIND,THEY GOTTA CUT RATES.
I THOUGHT I TOLD YOUTO DROP THIS 1% BULLSHIT.
I'VE BEEN RE-RUNNINGTHE NUMBERS, OKAY?
MY GUT IS TELLING ME--YOUR GUT?
YOU THINK THIS IS VEGASOR SOMETHING YOU CAN GO AROUNDBETTING YOUR GUT?
MARK, I'M SORRY,YOU'RE GONNA HAVE TO EXCUSEYOUNG MR. CONNER HERE.
IT SEEMS THAT HE HAS JUSTAWOKEN FROM DREAMLAND.
YOU DECREASE RATES, OKAY?CONSUMERS?
THEY'RE GONNA GO OUT,THEY'RE GONNA RE-FI THEIR HOMES,
THEY'RE GONNA HAVEA LOT OF CASH.
THEY'RE GONNA HAVE THE CASHTO BUY THE FLAT SCREEN TVs,
THE PHONES, THE GADGETS,WHATEVER THEY WANTFOR THEIR KIDS.
AND WHO MAKES THOSECONSUMER PRODUCTS? CHINA.
AND WHAT'S THE LARGEST COMPANYTHAT'S GONNA BENEFIT FROM THAT?
I'M SORRY, AM I THE ONLY ONEWHO THINKS THAT HE IS INFANTASY LAND RIGHT NOW?
THE FED WILL NEVER CUT RATESTO 1%. THEY NEVER HAVE,THEY NEVER WILL.
Mark: FIGURE IT OUTAND GET BACK TO ME.
IF YOU WOULD JUSTLISTEN TO ME--NO, YOU LISTEN TO ME!
FEI &amp; CHANG IS DEAD!
THIS MEETING'S OVER,GET THE FUCK OUT!
YOU THINK YOU'RE SO SMART,DON'T YOU?
YOU AND YOUR MAGIC NUMBERS.OH, GOD.
WELL, LET ME TELL YOU SOMETHING,YOU PULL ANOTHER STUNT IN THERELIKE THAT AGAIN,
THE ONLY MAGIC YOU'LL BE DOINGIS RUBBING MY MAGIC LAMP.
RUBBING YOUR MAGIC LAMP.GOT IT.
GOOD. ANDY,DUMP ALL FEI &amp; CHANGAT THE OPEN.
YOU'RE MAKING A MISTAKE.
( laughs ) WOW, WHAT MAKES YOUTHINK SOME PUNK COLLEGE DROPOUT
HAS THE PRIVILEGEOF TELLING ME WHAT TO DO?
I'VE BEEN COVERING YOUR SECTORFOR THE LAST SIX MONTHS,
I'VE BEEN DRAFTINGYOUR PROPOSALS, I'VE BEENCRUNCHING THE NUMBERS,
I'M PRETTY MUCHDOING YOUR JOB.
SO, YEAH, PERSONALLY?I THINK I DESERVE--
YOU KNOW,I DON'T GIVE A RAT'S ASSWHAT YOU PERSONALLY THINK.
YOU'RE MAKINGUNPRECEDENTED CALLSIN THE MARKET,
AND YOU'RE DOINGWHATEVER YOU WANT.
THERE'S A CHAINOF COMMAND HERE,
SO WHEN I SAY GO FUCK YOURSELF,YOU ASK HOW DEEP.
YOU GOT THAT?
MORRIS, LIGHTEN UP A BIT .
ANDY, IF I WANTEDSOME UNSOLICITED ADVICE
FROM A LITTLE BITCH,I'LL GO CALL MY EX-WIFE.
LET ME SPELL IT OUT FOR YOU.FED--1%.
FEI &amp; CHANG? MASSIVE UPSIDE.
OKAY. OKAY, SMARTASS.
YOU WANNA PUT YOUR MONEYWHERE YOUR MOUTH IS?
COME ON, WHATEVER.
TEN TO ONE ODDS.
YOU DON'T WANNA BE HEREAND I DON'T WANT YOU HERE.
SO I TELL YOU WHAT...
EVERYONE, LISTEN UPFOR A SECOND, LISTEN UP!
I, MORRIS BROWN III,
WILL HEREBY CONTRIBUTETO 'SHIT FOR BRAINS'--
THAT'S YOU--
THE SUM OF $50,000,
IF 'SHIT FOR BRAINS' HERE
RUNS AROUND THE OFFICEWITH HIS PANTS OFF,
SCREAMING"MORRIS IS MY DADDY."
COME ON, CONNER!
I WANNA SEE GRAPE-NUTS!HEY, I'LL DO IT!
CONNER! CONNER! CONNER!I'LL DO IT WITH YOU, CONNER!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING, MAN?
NOTHING IS WORTHYOUR SELF-RESPECT.
OH, THAT IS SO TOUCHING!
I SWEAR, I JUST DON'T KNOWWHAT MARK SEES IN YOU.
IF IT WERE UP TO ME, YOU'D BENOTHING MORE THAN THE GUY
PICKING THE CORNOUT OF MY BIG, WET SHIT.
BIG, WET SHIT. GOT IT.
MR. BROWN?MARK IS ON LINE ONE.
THANK YOU.
ANDY? DUMP IT.
Man: STOCKS ARE GETTINGA BOOST AFTER
THE FEDERAL RESERVE REDUCEDTHE COST OF BORROWING TO 1%.
THAT'S THE MOVE HERE.YOU'D HAVE TO GO BACK, WHAT?
TO THE 1940'STO SEE MONEY THIS CHEAP.
WHAT'S EXPECTED?RISING HOUSE PRICES.
AS A RESULT,MORE CONSUMER SPENDING.
INVESTORS REALLY AT THE MOMENTTRYING TO GRAPPLE
WITH THE FED'S MOVE HERE,TRYING TO MAKE SENSE OF IT.
ONE THING IS FOR CERTAIN,THOUGH--
THIS IS A MAJOR SHIFTIN MONETARY POLICY,
FOR THE U.S. ECONOMY,AND WAY, WAY BEYOND THAT.
LETS HAVE A LOOKAT THE MARKETS,
AND THEIR REACTION,IN A BIT MORE DETAIL.
LAURIE? GET MARKBACK ON THE LINE, WILL YOU?
ENJOY YOUR MEAL.
THANKS.
ONE PERCENT.WHO COULD HAVE PREDICTED THAT?
NOT A DAMN PERSON.
( door buzzes )
HEY THERE.
HEY.
WHAT DO YOU WANT, MARK?
I CAME TO GIVE YOU THIS.UH, MINUS FEES, OF COURSE.
WHAT IS THIS?IT'S YOUR EARNINGS FORSTICKING IT TO MORRIS TODAY.
LOOK, I DIDN'T GET TO BETHE MAN STANDING BEFORE YOUWITHOUT TAKING A FEW RISKS.
I TOOK THAT BETTHAT MORRIS LAID OUT,AND I TOOK A RISK ON YOU,
AND NOW ITS TIME FOR YOUTO TAKE A RISK ON YOURSELF.
SAVE THE DAD TALKFOR YOUR DAUGHTER, OKAY?
YOU EVER BEEN TO HONG KONG?
YOU EVEN BEENOUT OF THE COUNTRY, KIDDO?
WHAT? YOU GIVING METHE SILENT TREATMENT NOW?
I WANT YOU TO GO TO HONG KONG
AND LEADTHE FEI &amp; CHANG TRADE.
THAT'S MORRIS' TRADE.IT'S YOUR TRADE, NOW.
OH, COME ON, WHY ME?WHY DON'T YOU GET ONE
OF YOUR PRINCETON,INBRED SILVERMAN LACKEYS--
OH, DON'T PULLTHE COLLEGE CARD ON ME AGAIN.
YOU DROPPED OUT OF M.I.T.'CAUSE YOU FELT LIKE IT.
YOU'RE EXTREMELY GIFTED.
YOU HAVE THE EDGEYOUR FATHER HAD.
HE COULD BET AGAINST THE STREETAND BE RIGHT ABOUT IT.
YOU WANT TO KNOW THE DIFFERENCEBETWEEN HIM AND YOU?
SAVE IT.HE WAS A WINNER.
NEVER MADE ANY EXCUSES.
YOU THINK THAT JUST BECAUSE YOUCAN PREDICT A FEW RIGHT OUTCOMESTHAT THAT MAKES YOU A WINNER?
NO.
YOU'RE NOT A WINNER,UNTIL YOU DECIDE TO BE ONE.
LOOK, I'M NOT MY FATHER.
YOU WANT TO BET?
GO TO HONG KONG,
BE THE MANTHAT YOU WERE BORN TO BE.
Conner's Father: CONNER,I'LL ONLY BE GONE FOR 6 WEEKS.
I'LL CALL YOUWHEN I GET TO HONG KONG.
ONE DAY, YOU'LL UNDERSTAND.
Conner's Mother: CONNER?IT'S YOUR FATHER...
HE--HE'S...
( horn honks )
HEY, WATCH IT!
( airplane taking off )
FU YIN! WELCOME TOAMAZING HONG KONG, EVERYBODY!
♪ YEAH, WE EARLY, EARLY,EARLY RISERS ♪
♪ COME TAKE A JOURNEY WITH ME ♪
♪ SOME DAYHOPEFULLY ONE DAY SOON ♪
♪ I CAN FLY PAST THE SKYAND I TOUCH THE MOON ♪
♪ THEY SAY THE SKY'S THE LIMIT,BUT I'M LOOKING FAR BEYOND IT ♪
♪ AIMING FOR A COMET,MAKE A JUMP AND GRAB ON IT ♪
♪ MY HEART BEATING ♪
♪ THE BLOOD OF THE MOTHERLANDRUNNING THROUGH MY VEINS ♪
♪ LIKE THE SANDTHROUGH AN HOURGLASS ♪
♪ LOOK TO THE STARS... ♪
CONNER LEE.HEY, WELCOME TO HONG KONG.
HEY, YOU MUST BE QUENTIN.AH, DEPENDS ON WHO'S ASKING.
HOW LONG YOU BEEN OUT HERE FOR?OH, IN THIS PRISON?EIGHT YEARS.
COME ON, I'LL INTRODUCE YOUTO ALL THE INMATES.
BY THE WAY,HOW WAS THE BUS RIDE?
OH, IT WAS GREAT.GREAT?
( laughs )IT'S LAME AS SHIT.
I JUST WANTED YOU TO GETALL THAT TOURISTY CRAPOUT OF THE WAY.
YOU READY TO SEETHE REAL HONG KONG?
YOU BET.
AND HERE WE ARE.
THAT'S RAJ OVER THERE,COVERS INDIA.
HE'S A PUMP AND DUMPER.
JAMES. COVERS MALAYSIA,THAILAND, DISTRESSED DEBT.
THIS IS YOU. THIS IS ME.
SO, WHAT DO YOU TRADE?
I RUN ALL THE SHORT STRATEGIES.
SO YOU LIKE TO SEECOMPANIES BURN?
WHOA, HEY, COME ON!
SHIT HITS THE FANTHE SAME WAY IT DOESBACK IN NEW YORK.
HEY, SEXY!
OH, BY THE WAY, CAN YOU PLEASEALSO GET ME THAT 7588 FILE?
( laughs )
WHAT WAS THAT ALL ABOUT?
SLUT.I KNOW IT'S A LOT TO TAKE IN,
BUT DON'T WORRY,I GOT YOUR BACK, BRO.
BY THE WAY,WHERE'D YOU GET THAT SUIT?
LOOKS LIKE 7448 TO ME.
DID YOU SAY MY SUITLOOKS LIKE SHIT?
Quentin: OUT HERE,STEALTH WEALTH IS A MUST.
IT'S THE LITTLE THINGS THATSEPARATE YOU FROM THE REST.
FIRST IMPRESSIONS?NO, THAT'S BULLSHIT.
YOU ONLY GET ONE CHANCETO MAKE ANY KIND OF IMPRESSION.
THAT'S WHY WE WEAR THE BEST...
WE DRINK THE BEST...
WE DRIVE THE BEST...
AND WHEN IT COMES TO CHICKS,
WE ONLY DO THE BEST.
THE MOST IMPORTANT THINGWE MUST LEARN
IS THE ART OF GUAN XI.GUAN XI?
IT'S YOUR BASIC RELATIONSHIPSWITH PEOPLE.
LOOK, BRO,YOU'RE IN HONG KONG NOW.
NOTHING GETS DONEWITHOUT GIVING GREAT GUAN XI.
WELL, THAT AND ONE OF THESE.
COME MON.
♪ SHOW ME WHAT YOU GOT... ♪
Quentin:CONNER, MEET GARY.
GARY IS NOT ONLY THE FINANCIALCONTROLLER AT FEI &amp; CHANG,
HE'S ALSO A HELL OF A SAILOR.
JUST THE MANI WAS TALKING ABOUT.AH, QUENTIN!
NICE, ACTUALLYI COULD USE SOME REPORTS--
YOU KNOW WHAT?TOO MUCH TALKING. LET'S ENJOY!
GUAN XI, HUH?
YEAH.
HERE COMES YOURS NOW, BRO.
WELCOME TO HONG KONG.
NICE TO MEET YOU. I'M--
HEY, GARY.
HEY, CONNER.I GOT WHAT YOU NEED.
GREAT. IF YOU COULDJUST GIVE ME THE "P AND L"
ON THE SHIPPING DEPARTMENTAND PUT IT ON A USB DRIVE.
SORRY, IT'S GONNATAKE A WHILE.
THIS SYSTEM IS IN NEEDOF A COMPLETE UPDATE.NO PROBLEM.
FATHER, I REALLY DON'TTHINK WE SHOULD BE MAKINGTHAT DECISION RIGHT NOW.
( sighs )IT'S THE SAAM GWOK.
THE WHAT?THE THREE KINGDOMS.
DONALD THE CEO,VICTOR HIS OLDER BROTHER,
AND RICHARDTHE HEIR APPARENT.
YOU SHOULD GET GOING.I'LL TAKE THAT.
GARY, WHO IS THIS?
CONNER LEE.
LOOK, I WAS JUST TRYING TO GETSOME REPORTS HERE FROM GARY.
I WASN'T NOTIFIEDOF YOUR VISIT.
WELL, I DIDN'T WANTTO TROUBLE YOU WITHSUCH TRIVIAL MATTERS, RICHARD.
BUT STANDARD PROCEDUREAT THIS COMPANY IS FOR METO REVIEW ALL REPORTS FIRST.
GARY, NEXT TIME PLEASE INFORM MEOF ALL SPECIAL GUESTS
BEFORE GIVINGOUT PRIVATE INFORMATION.YES, SIR.
SO WHEN WILL I RECEIVETHE REPORTS?AT LEAST A MONTH.
A MONTH? I MEAN,THEY'RE JUST SIMPLE REPORTS.
WHAT YOU MIGHT VIEW AS SIMPLEMAY BE MORE COMPLEX TO OTHERS.
I CAN SEE THAT.
GLAD YOU'RE CLEAR.
ANITA, I THOUGHT I TOLD YOUMARK DOESN'T LIKE SALTON HIS EGGS!
SORRY, MA'AM.
A MONTH? WHAT'S THE HOLD UP?I THOUGHT YOU HAD THIS!
SWEETIE, WHO'S THATON THE PHONE?
IT'S CONNER.
HEY, CONNER!
HI, JULIET.
NO. NO GIRLFRIEND.
Mark:LOOK, I DON'T CARE
WHAT THE HOLD UP IS, ALL RIGHT?
WE HAVE A 5% SHAREIN THE COMPANY, FOR GOD'S SAKE.
WE CAN DO WHATEVER THE--
DADDY, CAN I HAVEA GLASS OF WATER?
YES, HONEY.
Conner: THAT DOESN'T SEEMTO MEAN ANYTHING TO HIM.
ALL RIGHT. WELL, IT SOUNDSLIKE HE'S GOT YOU DOWNON BOTH KNEES...
SO WHILE YOU'RE DOWN THERE,WHY DON'T YOU GIVE HIM A--
LOOK, I JUST NEEDMORE TIME, OKAY?
YEAH, FINE.
KEEP ME POSTED.
HEY, UH, CAN I GETA J.D. STRAIGHT UP?
MAY I?
IT'S A FREE COUNTRY.
THAT'S NOT WHAT I HEAR.
AND WHAT HAVE YOU HEARD?
WELL, IT'S HONG KONG,IT'S PRACTICALLY CHINA.
THEY CAN CHANGE THE SIDEOF THE ROAD YOU DRIVE ONJUST LIKE THAT IF THEY WANT TO.
AND WHERE ARE YOU FROM?
THE STATES.
SO YOU DON'T THINKTHE GOVERNMENTCONTROLS YOU THERE?
WE GOT A CONSTITUTION;FREEDOM OF SPEECH.
SO YOU DON'T THINKTHE GOVERNMENT USES MEDIATO CREATE FEAR AND PANIC
SO YOU'LL STAY INYOUR LITTLE BOX?
FEAR OF TERRORISM,NATURAL DISASTERS, ILLNESSES?
I'M SURPRISEDYOU'RE ABLE TO SLEEP AT NIGHT.
I'M CONNER.NATALIE WANG.
YOU SEEM TO KNOWA LOT ABOUT POLITICS.
I STUDIED POLITICAL SCIENCEAND NOW I JUST--
BUST PEOPLE'S BALLS, HUH?DO PUBLIC RELATIONS.
AH, SO YOU'REA PROFESSIONAL BALL BUSTER?
CAN I GET A GLASS OF RED WINEAND A COKE OVER TO THAT TABLEOVER THERE? THANKS.
YOU'RE WITH THAT GUY?NICE TALKING TO YOU, CONNER.
( grunts )LOVE IT! LOVE IT!
GIVE IT TO ME!LOVE THE ENERGY!
COME ON! UPPERCUTS!( grunts )
NICE, ONE MORE!( grunts )
HOW'S THE GUAN XI TODAY, BRO?
( speaking Cantonese )
( grunts )
DUDE, YOUR CHINESE SUCKS.
COME ON, WHAT'S EATING YOU?WHAT'S THE SCOOP?
THE CEO'S SON.
AH, RICHARD CHANG!
HE'S GOT ALL THE DATAUNDER LOCK AND KEY.
TYPICAL COCK-SUCKINGFAMILY HIERARCHY.
( grunts )ALWAYS GETTING IN THE WAYOF OUR MONEY.
( grunts )THE PRODIGAL SON,
TRYING TO WEAN HIMSELFFROM THE FAMILIAL TIT.
ALWAYS TRYING TO PROVETHAT HIS COCK IS BIGGERTHAN HIS DADDY'S.
( grunts )
WHAT DO YOU THINKI SHOULD DO?
HOW MUCH MONEY YOU GOT?
EH? ( chuckles )WHAT DO YOU THINK?
IT'S PRETTY NICE.
OKAY. WE'RE TALKINGHIGH-LEVEL QUAN XI.
RICHARD ALREADY HASMONEY AND POWER,
BUT YOU CAN'T BUY HIM OUT.
THE ONLY THING YOU CANTAKE FROM HIM IS HIS RESPECT.
DO THAT, AND HE MAYJUST GIVE YOU THE KEYSTO THE FEI &amp; CHANG CASTLE.
Quentin:LET'S GET YOU UP TO SPEEDBECAUSE TONIGHT,
IT LOOKS LIKEYOU'RE GOING MANO Y MANO.
THE GAME DU JOURIS BACCARAT.
IT'S SIMPLE. YOU CAN BETEITHER BANKER OR PLAYER.
EACH SIDE GETS TWO CARDS.
ADD THEM UP,DROP THE FIRST DIGIT,
AND THAT'S A POINT.
CLOSEST TO NINE WINS.
IF YOU CAME HERE FOR ANYTHINGTO DO WITH THE COMPANY--
NO, I JUST CAMETO PLAY SOME CARDS.
FINE.
FUN GAME.
GOD, YOU'RE SO AMERICAN.
I AM AMERICAN.
AND YOU WANT EVERYTHINGRIGHT AWAY AND YOU THINKYOU'RE ALWAYS RIGHT,
THAT YOU ARE ENTITLEDTO WHATEVER YOU WANT
AND YOU CANTAKE AS YOU PLEASE,
WITH NO PATIENCE,NO CONSEQUENCE.
YOU'RE THE BLINDLEADING THE BLIND.
NO TIES TO FAMILY,OR OF HERITAGE NOR TRADITION.
YOU THINKYOU KNOW EVERYTHING,
WHEN YOU HAVENO UNDERSTANDING OF ANYTHING.
( men chanting )
YEAH!
( applause )
WANT TO GO AGAIN?
YOU BET.
( woman giggles )
( sighs )
( door opens )
( laughing )
WHOA. WINNER WINNER,DIM SUM DINNER.
WHAT HAPPENED TO YOU?
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT,GO WAIT OUTSIDE. COME ON.
WHAT HAPPENED?
I JUST LOST A HUNDRED THOUSAND.OW.
EVERY TIME I BET, HE JUSTBETS AGAINST ME AND WINS.
RELAX.YOU CAN DO THIS, BRO.
YOU EVER PLAYBOTH SIDES BEFORE?WHAT?
LOOK, FIRST YOU BETBOTH PLAYER AND BANKER.
FORCE HIM TO DECIDE.
AFTER HE'S CHOSEN,
YOU BET THE REST OFWHAT YOU HAVE AGAINST HIM.
ARE YOU SERIOUS?WHAT ABOUT THE TREND?
FUCK THE TREND. PLAY WHATYOU HAVE IN FRONT OF YOU.
SHAKE IT UP.LIVE A LITTLE.
YOU REALLY SHOULDJUST GIVE UP NOW.
AND SPOIL ALL THE FUN?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
BEING AMERICAN.
WELL, PLEASE,BY ALL MEANS,
KEEP PUMPINGYOUR AMERICAN DOLLARSINTO OUR ECONOMY.
THAT'S THE ONLY REASONWE LET YOUR KIND IN HERE.
HOW ABOUTWE MAKE THIS INTERESTING?
I WIN; YOU GIVE ME THE NUMBERSI NEED TO DO MY JOB.
I LOSE...YOU LOSE...
WHAT COULD YOU POSSIBLY HAVETHAT I DON'T ALREADY OWN?
I LOSE; ME AND MYAMERICAN DOLLARS GO HOME.
DEAL.
PLAYER WINS.
( sighs )
NO HARD FEELINGS.
YOUR INTENTIONS BETTER BEAS GOOD AS YOUR LUCK.
YEAH. NO, HE'S DOING GOOD.HE'S DOING REALLY GOOD.
OH, HEY I GOTTA GO.
DID IT WORK?
YEAH, BRO.
REALLY?
YES, REALLY.
( laughs ) DAMN!
I GUESS WE GOTSOMETHING CELEBRATE.
( laughs )
( dialing )
( ringing )
WHAT DO YOU HAVE FOR ME?
Conner: ALL RIGHT.SO, RETAIL OUTLETS SEEM FINE.
SOME FACTORIESARE LOSING MONEY,
BUT IT SEEMSTHE IMPORT/EXPORT BUSINESS
HAS SOMESERIOUS CASH FLOW ISSUES,
AND THAT'S WHATI WANT TO TARGET.
RIGHT NOW,THEY'VE BEEN WORKING WITH
SILVERMAN INVESTMENT BANKERSTO COVER THEIR DEBT.
DONALD HAS BEEN RELUCTANTTO TAKE ON THIS RISK.
THIS TYPE OF INDECISIVENESSHAS SHAREHOLDERS FED UP,
KEEPING THE STOCK PRICE DOWN.
IT'S A FAMILY-RUN COMPANY
WITH YOUNGER BROTHER DONALDSWIFTLY LOSING CONTROL.
NOW, THE COMPANYHAS BEEN CAPITALIZING
ON ALL THE GROWTHOF THE U.S.,
BUT THEY'VE BEEN HELD BACK
BECAUSE MANAGEMENTCAN'T SEEM TO KEEP COSTS DOWN.
WITH THE SPECIFIC CHANGESI'VE GOT LINED UP,
I'D SAY THE STOCKCOULD JUMP AT LEAST 20 TO 30%.
THIRTY PERCENT, SOUNDS GOOD.KEEP ME POSTED. GOTTA GO.
RIGHT.
( beeps )
( rings )
CONNER!HEY!
EVERYONE'S BETTINGYOU'D BE SENT HOME BY NOW.
WELL, INCREASE MY POSITIONON FEI &amp; CHANG
TO 200 MILLION.
TWO HUNDRED BUCKSON FEI &amp; CHANG?
THOUGHT YOU'RE ONLY AUTHORIZEDTO DO A HUNDRED.
BOTTOM OF THE NINTH, BUDDY.TIME TO CALL MY SHOT.
OKAY, YOU'RE THE BOSS.
( woman speaking Cantonese )
THANK YOU.
THEY SHOULDN'T BE MUCH LONGER.CAN I OFFER YOU A COFFEE?
NO, THANKS.
( video game noises )
HEY, KID.
WHAT?
WANT TO KNOW A SECRET?OKAY.
( whispering ) They're tryingto kill me with coffee.
REALLY?Yeah.
See, if I hadn't drankso much coffee
when I was younger,I'd be a giant.
COOL!
I'D BE A GIANT! ( roars )
I'M GOING TO EAT YOU UP AND--
MR. LEE?UH...
WE'RE READYFOR YOU NOW.RIGHT.
BYE, NATALIE.OH, I'LL SEE YOU!
OKAY, SEE YOU TOMORROW.OKAY, BYE!
COME ON, LETS GO.
SO IN SUMMARY,I RECOMMEND YOU, ONE:
CLOSE DOWN THESE NINE FACTORIES.
TWO: TERMINATE SEVERALPOOR-PERFORMING MANAGERS,
LISTED IN APPENDIX B.
AND MOST IMPORTANTLY, THREE:
SELL OFFTHE IMPORT/EXPORT BUSINESS
FOR ITS NEGATIVE CASH FLOW.
MR. LEE.
THE LIST OF THE MANAGERS HERE,I WILL NOT FIRE ANY OF THEM.
AND THESE WORKERSIN THE FACTORIES THAT YOUWANT US TO CLOSE DOWN?
THEY HAVE FAMILIES,SONS AND DAUGHTERS TO SUPPORT.
NOT ONLY THAT,
THEY ARE ALL PARTOF MY BIG FAMILY.
I THINK YOU'RE MISSINGTHE POINT HERE.
SEE, THE FACTORIES,THEY'RE INEFFICIENT AND BLOATED.
IN ANY EVENT,I'M MORE CONCERNED ABOUTTHE IMPORT/EXPORT BUSINESS.
DO YOU KNOW ANYTHING ABOUTTHE IMPORT/EXPORT BUSINESS?
THERE ARE HIGHS AND LOWS.RIGHT NOW HAPPENS TO BE A LOW.
FOR THE LAST THREE YEARS?
YOU ARE ASKING METO ELIMINATE
AN INTEGRAL PARTOF MY COMPANY--
THAT COULD EVENTUALLY BRING DOWNTHE REST OF THE COMPANY.
FATHER, YOU CAN'T SERIOUSLYALLOW THIS GUY TO MANHANDLETHE FATE OF THE COMPANY.
THE FACT THAT YOU'REEVEN CONSIDERING--
RICHARD...
I THINK I SPEAKFOR THE BOARD.
YOU KNOW WHAT? ACTUALLY,I'D LIKE TO HEAR FROMTHE BOARD THEMSELVES.
YOUR PLAN WILL SIMPLY NOT WORK.
LOOK, I'VE RUN THE NUMBERS
AND RESPECTFULLYMAKE THE CHANGESOR SOMEONE ELSE WILL.
SOMEONE ELSE?
ARE YOU THREATENING ME,MR. LEE?
IT'S NOT A THREAT,IT'S A PLAIN FACT.
LOOK, YOU THINK THATJUST BECAUSE YOUR FATHER
GAVE YOU THE COMPANYA LONG TIME AGO
YOU CAN JUST SWEEP THISALL UNDER THE RUG?
WHAT DO YOU KNOWABOUT FAMILY, MR. LEE?
ENOUGH TO SEE THATIT'S SKEWING YOUR JUDGMENT.
I DON'T LIKE YOUR TONE!( inaudible whisper )
GOOD DAY, MR. LEE!
I'M NOT FINISHED.I THINK YOU ARE, MR. LEE.
FATHER, JUST LISTEN TO WHATI HAVE TO SAY FOR ONCE,WITHOUT BEING SO THICK-HEADED.
ENOUGH! PLEASE, EVERYBODY OUT!
RICHARD! RICHARD! RICHARD!
NOW, YOU MUST LEARNWHICH BATTLE TO FIGHT.
( speaking Cantonese )
HE NEVER LISTENS.
COMES FROM YOUR GRANDMOTHER.
I JUST WANT HIM TO KNOWTHAT THERE'S ANOTHER WAY.
RICHARD, I WANT TO KNOW...
( speaking Cantonese )
...OR SOME NEW TECHNOLOGYWHICH I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
ALL I WANT TO KNOW IS,HOW IS IT COMING?ALMOST FINISHED.
IT'S GOING TO REVOLUTIONIZETHE INDUSTRY, AND HE WON'TEVEN LISTEN.
( speaking Cantonese )
EVERY NIGHT.
GREAT.
PERFECT IT.MAKE IT WORK.
( speaking Cantonese )
THIS TIME I'M GONNAMAKE HIM LISTEN.
ALL FOR THE FAMILY, RIGHT?
FOR THE FAMILY.
( phone rings )
KEEP ME INFORMED. OKAY?
( speaking Cantonese )
Conner: YEAH, I THOUGHT THEY'DAGREE TO SOME OF THE CHANGES.
WELL, I'M SURE YOU'LLFIGURE SOMETHING OUT.
REALLY? I MEAN...
I JUST DON'T KNOWIF I'M CUT OUT FOR THIS.
LOOK, YOU ARE DOING EXACTLYWHAT YOU SHOULD BE DOING.
THANKS.
YOU KNOW, SOMETIMES YOU PUSH
WHEN REALLY WHAT YOU NEED TO DOIS PULL.
AND GOING IN FROM THE FRONT DOORHASN'T BEEN WORKING.
MAYBE THERE'S A SIDE DOOR?
YEAH, KEEP GOING.
WELL, DONALD'S GOT A LOTOF LEGACIES TO MAINTAIN,
AND HALF HIS FAMILYPRACTICALLY RUNS THE JOINT.
WHY DON'T WE GET SOMEBODYFROM THE OUTSIDE TO INVESTIGATE?
SHAKE IT UP A LITTLE.
YEAH, SHAKE IT UP A LITTLE.
I LIKE THE WAY YOU'RE THINKING.KEEP GOING.
( beeps )
( sighs)
CAN YOU BELIEVETHIS GUY'S SHIRT, HUH?
( speaking Cantonese )
Conner: DEAR MR. JANG,VICE PRESIDENT OF OPERATIONS.
WE HAVE ATTAINED MATERIALSOF YOUR POTENTIAL INVOLVEMENT
IN ILLEGAL ACTIVITIES REGARDINGFEI &amp; CHANG ENTERPRISES.
MANY KEY EMPLOYEESHAVE ALREADY TESTIFIED,
AND WE ARE FORCEDTO TAKE IMMEDIATE ACTION.
WE'VE THUS NOTIFIEDTHE INDEPENDENT COMMISSIONAGAINST CORRUPTION.
LORRAINE IP.
IN RECOGNITIONOF YOUR CONTRIBUTIONTO THE COMPANY THUS FAR,
WE ARE OFFERING YOU THE OPTIONTO RESIGN FROM YOUR POST,
ELSE, PROSECUTIONBY THE COMPANY
AND THE HONG KONG GOVERNMENTSHALL BE HELD
TO THE FULLEST EXTENTWITHOUT LENIENCY.
I'M IN CORPORATE SALES--
YOU KNOW, TAKE CLIENTS OUT,MAKE SURE THEY'RE ENTERTAINED.
I SEE.
RESPECTFULLY YOURS,AN INDEPENDENT THIRD PARTY
ACTING ON BEHALF OFTHE COMPANY FEI &amp; CHANGAND ITS SHAREHOLDERS.
( door opens and closes )
( speaking Cantonese )
YOU'RE A DISGRACETO YOUR FATHER'S MEMORY.
♪ MONEY AND THE POWER,MONEY AND THE POWER ♪
I REALLY DIDN'T THINKYOU HAD IT IN YOU.
YOU HAVE GOT THOSEFEI &amp; CHANG PANSIES
RUNNING AROUND WITH THEIRPANTIES AROUND THEIR ANKLES!
( all laugh )
HEY, YOU SEE THAT DUDEOVER THERE?YEAH.
THAT'S MY BUDDY"DIU LE LO MO."
HE'S THE MAN AROUND HERE,REALLY FRIENDLY GUY.
GO INTRODUCE YOURSELF.
OKAY.
HEY! DIU LE LO MO!
HEY? DIU LE LO MO!
HUH?
( speaking Cantonese )
WHOA! HEY...YOU ALL RIGHT?
YEAH.
HEY, WHY DON'T YOU SITYOUR PUNK ASS DOWN?
( scoffs )
( speaking Cantonese )
( laughs )
WHAT THE FUCK, DUDE?
CHINESE LESSONS!
WHAT'D I SAY?"GO FUCK YOUR MOM."
All: OOH!
BUT HEY,SPEAKING OF MOTHERS...
HOLD THAT THOUGHT,WE GOT SOMETHING FOR YOU.
ALL RIGHT.
All: HAPPY BIRTHDAY!
WHA--
HOW'D YOU GUYS...?
I'M THE KING OF INTEL, BRO.
MAKE A WISH.
( blows )
All: CHEERS!
HAPPY BIRTHDAY TO ME.
James: OH, YEAH, YOU WISH!
WHATEVER, MAN,YOU LIKE BOYS!
GO BACK HIM UP, JAMES.
HEY, I THINK WE STARTED OFFON THE WRONG FOOT.
DO I KNOW YOU?
WELL, THAT DEPENDS...
LOOK, IT'S MY BIRTHDAY.
DO YOU MIND JOINING USFOR A DRINK?
I DON'T DRINK WITHNEANDERTHAL BANKERS.
LOOK, I THINK YOU HAVE MEMISTAKEN FOR SOMEBODY ELSE.
LET'S SEE. YOU'RE A TRADER,SUPERCAPITALIST INC.,
TRYING TO DISSOLVE A COMPANY
SO HE CAN GAIN MONETARY REWARDSIN THE SHORT TERM
WHILE DESTROYING LIVESIN THE LONG TERM.
( blows )DOES THAT ABOUT SUM IT UP?
WOW, THAT GUY SOUNDSLIKE A REAL ASSHOLE.
NO, I'M A FARMER.
A FARMER?
YEAH, I HAVE A LITTLE PLOTOF LAND IN CHINA,
GROW CORN,CONVERT IT TO BIOFUEL,
HELP MAKE THE WORLDA BETTER PLACE.
CONNER? CUT THE CRAP.
SO YOU DO REMEMBER ME?
YEAH, I REMEMBER YOU MAKINGA COMPLETE ASSHOLE OF YOURSELFIN THE BOARDROOM.
HEY, I'M JUST TRYINGTO MAKE PEACE HERE.
MAKE PEACE? YOU MAKE PEACE?
NO, MORE LIKE YOU WANT A PIECE.
I KNOW GUYS LIKE YOU.YOU THINK YOU'RE ALL ENTITLED.
GROW UP IN A RICH FAMILY,GO TO AN IVY LEAGUE SCHOOL...
YOU SHOW UP IN ASIA, THINKINGTHE WORLD IS YOUR PLAYGROUND.
...BEHIND YOUR EARS,TAKE SOME OF THAT HAIR--
COME ON, LET'S GET OUT OF HERE.
SAVED BY THE SLAP.
( chuckles )FUNNY.
LOOK, IF YOU'RE REALLY SERIOUSABOUT MAKING A DIFFERENCE,
HERE'S MY CARD.
OH HO HO HO! DO I HAVEA GOOD ONE FOR YOU TODAY!
FEI &amp; CHANG ENTERPRISES!
SELL YOUR BABIES,SELL YOUR CHILDREN,
SELL YOUR GIRLFRIEND!YOUR LIFE IS OVER!
FEI &amp; CHANG?MORE LIKE FEI &amp; BANG
'CAUSE YOU'RE ( bleep )!
♪ WE READY, SET, GET GO ♪
♪ WE JUST MET, GET LOW ♪
♪ TEXT IT ON MY CELL PHONE ♪
♪ GOT MY GIRLS TO PARTY, HELLO ♪
♪ WE OUT LIKEIT'S OUR LAST NIGHT ♪
♪ WE HIGHLIKE IT'S A SPACE FLIGHT ♪
♪ POP BOTTLESSO WE DO IT RIGHT ♪
♪ GOES UNTILTHE MORNING LIGHT ♪
♪ FEELING LIKE A MILLION... ♪
THE BIG FINANCIAL NEWSOF COURSE IS FEI &amp; CHANG
AND THE FUTUREOF ITS CEO DONALD CHANG.
( speaking Cantonese )
I'VE LOST MONEY FIVE YEARSIN A ROW, SO ABSOLUTELY.
( engine revs )
♪ EVERYTHING'S FOR ME ♪
♪ MY SWAGGER'S ALWAYS ON ♪
♪ THIS IS MY CITY ♪♪ IT'S MY CITY ♪
♪ TONIGHT WE'RE GONNAGET OURSELVES CRUNK ♪
♪ DANCE TILLTHE MORNING LIGHT... ♪
Michael:IT'S CALLED A POISON PILL.
ESSENTIALLY WE'RE DILUTINGTHE NUMBER OF SHARESCURRENTLY ON THE MARKET.
WHEN WE INCREASETHE NUMBER OF SHARES,THE STOCK PRICE GOES DOWN.
SO BASICALLY WHATYOU'RE SAYING IS,
I SHOULD INCREASETHE NUMBER OF SHARES AVAILABLE
IN ORDER TO HURTTHE SHARE PRICE?
EXACTLY! AND WHENTHE STOCK PRICE GOES DOWN--
HE LOSES MONEY.
HELL,EVERYBODY LOSES MONEY,
AT LEAST INTHE SHORT TERM.
LOOK, I KNOW THESEHEDGE FUND GUYS.
AS SOON AS THE STOCK PRICEGOES DOWN, HE'LL LIQUIDATE.
AND IF I DO THIS,WHAT ARE MY RISKS?
RISK? YOUR LEADERSHIPWOULD BE HIGHLY QUESTIONED!
YOU WILL LOSE THE CONTROLOF EVERYTHING!
RICHARD, THIS IS NOT THE TIME!
IF NOT, WHEN?FATHER, PLEASE. I HAVE AN IDEA.
MR. CHAU AND I HAVE BEENWORKING ON THIS PROGRAM--
RICHARD, WE NEED RESULTS,NOT YOUR CRAZY IDEAS.
THEY'RE NOT CRAZY!WHAT'S CRAZY IS THAT YOUARE TALKING TO THIS GUY!
WHAT ARE YOU LOOKING AT?RICHARD, I'M NOTGOING TO LISTEN.
YOU ARE EMBARRASSING ME.JUST GO.
COME ON,MAKE HIM LISTEN!RICHARD...
SORRY, MR. BAKER.
AH, FAMILY, WHAT YOU GONNA DO?
FACT OF THE MATTER IS,
YOU STILL HAVE TO PAY DOWNTHOSE DEBTS WE DISCUSSED.
THIS JUST GIVES YOU ALLTHE MORE REASON TO DO SO NOW.
I UNDERSTAND.
SO WHERE DID IT ALL GO WRONG?
( sighs )SEEMS LIKE FROM THE START.
WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
( speaking Cantonese )
IT DOESN'T MATTER.I UNDERSTAND. IT'S ALL RIGHT.
WHAT THEN?YOU'LL TAKE OVER FOR ME?
( speaking Cantonese )
AND I AM SURE FATHERIS VERY PROUD OF YOU.
( lights cigar )
( speaking Cantonese )
HE HAS SO MUCH CONTEMPT FOR ME.I CAN'T EVEN RELATE TO HIM.
YOU DON'T EVER HAVETO APOLOGIZE TO ME.
FUCKING BRILLIANT!
THEY'RE ON THE RUN.
Conner:GOT THE MARKETS IN A FRENZY.
STOCK'S UP 10%.I'M GONNA TAKE THE GAIN.
NO, NO, NO, NO.DON'T SELL, DON'T SELL.
KEEP THE PRESSURE ON.THIS IS GOOD.
YEAH, WHAT I TELL YOUABOUT TAKING RISKS?
I NEED A BIG TRADE OUT THERETO SHOW THESE INVESTORS,
AND THIS IS THE ONE.
ALL RIGHT, I GOTTA GO, CHAMP.
OKAY.
( beeps )
YEAH, IT'S ME.
NOW LOOK, YOU SAIDTHIS WAS GUARANTEED.
I HAVE THE ENTIRE FUNDRIDING ON THIS TRADE.
IF I GO DOWN,YOU GO DOWN.
GET IT DONE.
HEY, THANKS FOR MEETING ME.
SO WHAT DO YOU WANT, CONNER?
WELL, WITH ALL THE PRESSTHAT'S BEEN GOING ON,
I JUST THOUGHTWE SHOULD TALK.
TALK? YOU WANT ME TO TELL YOUEVERYTHING I KNOW
AND THEN AFTER HAVE A DRINKOR TWO UP IN YOUR HOTEL ROOM?
YEAH, I'M SORRY, NATALIE.I WISH WE MET UNDERDIFFERENT CIRCUMSTANCES.
DIFFERENT CIRCUMSTANCESWOULDN'T HAVE CHANGED ANYTHING.
SO YOU GOT MEALL FIGURED OUT, HUH?
YOU ASSUMEI'M THIS MONSTER.
YOU THINK ANY OTHER FUND'SGONNA TREAT YOU ANY DIFFERENTLY?
IF IT'S NOT ME,IT'S GONNA BE SOMEBODY ELSE.
THAT IS SO IRRESPONSIBLE.
AND THAT'S THE THINGTHAT GOT US INTO THIS MESSIN THE FIRST PLACE.
FOR SOMEONE THAT ACTSLIKE YOU KNOW EVERYTHING,THAT IS YOUR BEST ANSWER?
LOOK, I TRIED,NATALIE, OKAY?
AND I'M THE GUYJUST TRYING TO MAKE A PAYCHECK.
AT WHAT COST?
ACTIONS HAVE CONSEQUENCES,CONNER.
I'D AT LEAST RESPECT YOUIF YOU OWN UP TOYOUR OWN CHOICES.
I'M JUST TRYINGTO DO THE BEST I CANIN THE BEST WAY I KNOW HOW.
YEAH, I'M SURE.
CONVINCE ME.CHALLENGE ME.
COME ONE,MAKE ME UNDERSTAND FOR ONCE.
DON'T JUST WRITE ME OFFLIKE EVERYBODY ELSE.
WELL, HOW DO I KNOWI CAN TRUST YOU?
HOW DO I KNOW THATANYTHING I SHOW YOU
YOU'RE NOT GOINGTO USE AGAINST ME?
WELL, FIRST OF ALL...
YES, I DID GO TOAN IVY LEAGUE COLLEGE.
WHEN I WAS WORKINGWITH A PROFESSOR,
I HAPPENEDTO PROVE HIM WRONG.
SO HE FLUNKED ME.
LOOK, I KNOWWHAT IT'S LIKE WHEN SOMEONEDOESN'T BELIEVE IN YOU.
IF YOU'VE GOT A SOLUTIONTHAT MAKES SENSE, I'LL LISTEN.
THERE IS ANOTHER WAY.
BUT IF I LET YOU IN ON IT,IT'S GONNA CHALLENGE YOUR VIEWS,
AND THEN YOU'RE GONNAHAVE TO MAKE A DECISION.
I CALLED YOU, REMEMBER?
LOOK, IF YOU GOT SOMETHINGTHAT MAKES SENSE,
I'LL BE THE FIRST TO SPEAK UP.
OKAY, I'LL SET UPAN APPOINTMENT.
GREAT.
WE SHOULD REALLY ORDER.
YEAH, GREAT.
I DON'T...
YES, I KNOW. I FORGOT.YEAH.
USELESS.
GIZZARDS, LUNG,INTESTINE.
CLOTTED BLOOD.
ALL RIGHT, YOU ORDER.
( speaking Cantonese )
( Natalie laughs )
SO, UH, THANKS FORSHOWING ME THAT SPOT.FOOD WAS DELICIOUS.
WELL, THERE'S MORE TO HONG KONGTHAN WHAT YOUR PALS SHOW YOU.
MAYBE I NEED A NEW PAL.
NICE TRY, CONNER.
NO, I THINKAS WORKING COLLEAGUES,IT'S GOOD WE ESTABLISH--
WAIT, HOLD ON, HOLD ON.THIS IS A FIRST DATE, RIGHT?
WE'RE NOT WORKING COLLEAGUES.
DON'T PUSH YOUR LUCK, CONNER.
WELL, I'M GLADWE FINALLY MADE PEACE.
OR SO YOU THINK.
NO, WE'VE ONLYJUST BEGUN, CONNER.
WELL, THIS IS ME.THANKS FOR WALKING ME HOME.
MY PLEASURE.
YOU REALLY DIDN'T HAVE TO,BUT THANK YOU.
I WANTED TO.
GOODNIGHT, CONNER.
GOODNIGHT.
HEY, THINK ABOUTWHAT I SAID, OKAY?
I WILL. I PROMISE.
( speaking Cantonese )
HEY, YOU ALL RIGHT?
( speaking Cantonese )WHAT?
YOU SHOULD GO BACKTO WHERE YOU CAME FROM.
( speaking Cantonese )
( hits wall )
AH, MR. LEE. THANK YOUFOR COMING TO SEE ME.
LET'S JUSTGET THIS OVER WITH.
I TAKE IT YOU'VE DECIDEDTO MAKE THE CHANGES?
YOU KNOW, YOU NEARLYHAD ME CONVINCED.
AND THENI REALIZED SOMETHING.
AND IT ALL BECAMEVERY CLEAR TO ME.
HOW WELL DO YOUKNOW MY COMPANY?
INHERITED THE COMPANYFROM YOUR FATHER,
MADE ACQUISITIONSIN THE '80s,
WENT PUBLIC IN 1992.YES.
AND I BET YOU CAN TELL MEHOW MANY WORKERS I HAVE,HOW MANY FACTORIES I HAVE,
WHAT MY TOTAL REVENUE WASLAST YEAR.
25,320 WORKERS, 30 FACTORIES,1.7 BILLION.
AND YOU THINKYOU KNOW MY COMPANY
BECAUSE YOU READ A REPORT.
MR. LEE, LOOK OUT THERE.
THOUSANDS OF CONTAINERS.
BEYOND THE CONTAINERSARE THOUSANDS OF PEOPLE.
IT TOOK MEA LONG TIME TO LEARN
THAT IT'S THE PEOPLETHAT MATTERS,
IT'S THE PEOPLE THAT MAKESA BUSINESS A SUCCESS,
NOT IDEAS.
IT'S THE PEOPLEWE SHOULD CARE ABOUT.
WITH THE AMOUNT OF SHARESYOU NOW HAVE
COMES THE POWERTO WIELD THAT MIGHTY SWORD.
THAT SWORD CAN UNITEOR DESTROY MY COMPANY.
MR. LEE,I JUST WANT TO REMIND YOU...
THE CHOICE IS YOURS.
HEY.
THANKS FOR COMING.
A PROMISE IS A PROMISE.
Natalie:UNCLE? WE'RE HERE!
HI, NATALIE!HI!
HOW ARE YOU?
AH, THIS MUST BETHE INFAMOUS MR. LEE.
GOOD TO MEET YOU.
CONNER, THIS IS MR. CHAU,V.P. OF TECH.
WELCOME, WELCOME.
AND I THINK YOU'VEALREADY MET KELVIN.
( roars )
LETS SHOW HIM WHATWE'VE BEEN WORKING ON.
OKAY, LET GETTHINGS SET UP.COME ON, HAVE A SEAT.
HELLO, LITTLE MAN.
( speaking Cantonese )
SO, UH, WHAT KIND OF GAMEYOU GOT THERE?
OH! IT'S AN ONLINE GAME.IT'S REALLY FUN.
SEE, YOU CAN BUY COMPANIESAND SELL COMPANIES.
AND YOU CAN USE THOSE MONEYTHAT YOU EARN TO BUYOTHER COOL STUFF.
LIKE BOATS, CARS, AND HOUSES.
THE MORE MONEY I EARN,THE HIGHER MY STATUS.
WELL, I GOT A GAME FOR YOU.
YEAH?
READY? ROCK, PAPER...SCISSORS!
( chuckles )YOU KNOW THIS GAME.
ALL RIGHT.YEAH.
Both: ROCK, PAPER, SCISSORS!
ROCK, PAPER, SCISSORS!
YES, GOT YOU!OH!
OKAY, I'M ALL SET.
HERE, HAVE A SEAT.
ALL RIGHT.SEE...
RICHARD AND NATALIEAND I'VE BEEN WORKINGFOR THE PAST FEW MONTHS
ON THIS NEW SUPPLY CHAINMANAGEMENT SYSTEM.
YOU KNOW, I MODELEDTHE WHOLE SYSTEM AFTERKELVIN'S GAME OVER THERE.
SO GIVE EACH EMPLOYEEMORE INCENTIVE TO BE RESPONSIBLE
FOR THEIR OWN SHIPMENTSAND CONTAINERS...
IN A FUN AND EASY FORMAT.
WHY HAVEN'T YOU GUYSTOLD ANYBODY ABOUT THIS?
WELL, IT WAS RICHARD'S IDEA,
BUT DONALD HASN'T REALLYLISTENED TO RICHARDFOR A WHILE NOW.
DAD, CAN MR. LEESTAY FOR DINNER?
AH, YOU READ MY MIND!
OH, WE COULDN'T POSSIBLY--
WE'D LOVE TO.
( no audio )
HI.
HEY.
THIS IS NICE.YOU'RE REALLY DOING IT RIGHT.
WELL, IT TOOK MEA LONG TIME TO GET IT.
WORKING ALL THE TIME...FOR WHAT? FOR MONEY?
IS THERE ANYTHING ELSEONE COULD ASK FORIN THIS LIFETIME?
AM I INTERRUPTING ANYTHING?
OF COURSE NOT.
UM, IN FACT, I NEED TO GET INAND GET SOMETHING CHECKED ON.
( both chuckle )
I DON'T KNOW IF YOUMIND ME ASKING, BUT WHATWERE YOUR PARENTS LIKE?
DAD DIED WHEN I WAS EIGHT.
MOM TOOK CARE OF METHE BEST THAT SHE COULD.
MY DAD WAS A TRADER ONTHE NEW YORK STOCK EXCHANGE.
USED TO SPENDA LOT OF TIME HERE, THOUGH.
ONE DAY,HE JUST NEVER CAME BACK.
HOW ABOUT YOUR MOM?
SHE HATED THE STATES.
WHEN I TURNED 18,SHE JUST MOVED AWAY.
HAVEN'T SEEN HER SINCE.
DO YOU MISS HER?
YOU SHOULD TAKE THE TIMETO GET TO KNOW YOUR MOMBEFORE IT'S TOO LATE.
IT MUST HAVE BEEN REALLY HARDFOR YOU TO COME BACK HERE.
AND AFTER ALL THIS, YOU STILLDECIDED TO BECAME A TRADER.
HE USED TO LOVE TO GAMBLE.
HE USED TO GAMBLEAT THIS LOCAL MAHJONG PARLORIN CHINATOWN.
HE USED TO SAY,
( deep voice )"IF YOU AREN'T GAMBLING,YOU AREN'T LIVING."
( both chuckle )
( deep voice )JUST LIKE THAT?
( deep voice ) YES.
( both laugh )
THAT'S ALL I HAVE LEFT OF HIM.
IT'S A WORN OUTPIECE OF PLASTIC...
BUT IT GIVES ME PEACE.
I THINK THIS IS WHATHE WOULD'VE WANTED, YOU KNOW.
AND WHAT DO YOU WANT?
I DON'T KNOW ANYMORE.
UNCLE CONNER!READ ME A BEDTIME STORY!
( both chuckle )
HI, KELVIN.
HI.HI.
SAVED BY THE SLAP.
( chuckles )RIGHT.
LITTLE MAN, I'M GONNA HAVETO TEACH YOU A LITTLE THINGCALLED TIMING.
( no audio )
( screams )
Andy: CONNER.WHAT'S UP, BRO?
BRO? SINCE WHENDID YOU USE "BRO"?
WHAT'S UP, ANDY?
LISTEN, MAN, I WASFILLING ORDERS THE OTHER DAY
WHEN I NOTICEDSOME SHORT POSITIONSOUT OF NOWHERE ON YOUR TRADE.
WHO RUNS THE SHORTS OUT THERE?QUENTIN. BUT HE WOULDN'T--
THEY'RE ALL COMINGFROM AN ASIA TRADING DESKTHROUGH AN OFFSHORE ACCOUNT.
YOU HAVE ANY PROOF?
I CAN'T BE SURE. I MEAN...
I'D HAVE TO RUNOUR IN-HOUSE RECORDS WITHTHE RECORDS FROM FEI &amp; CHANG.
FEI &amp; CHANG? YOU KNOWHOW HARD IT IS TO GET ANYINFORMATION OUT OF FEI &amp; CHANG?
CONNER, THIS IS LARGE.
LOOK, MAN, WHEN I ADD UPALL THE SHORTS,
THE POSITION IS A BILLION U.S.
OUR POSITIONIS 200 MILLION.
ALL I'M SAYING IS THATSOMETHING IS DEFINITELYGOING DOWN OUT THERE,
AND THE STOCK PRICEIS A LIKELY CANDIDATE.
JUST WATCH YOUR BACK.
( beeps )
HEY.
CONNER, HEY, HOW ARE YOU?
THIS IS MICHAEL.
HEY, CONNER.
HEY, UH, I DIDN'T KNOWTHIS WAS A GROUP LUNCH.
COME ON, HAVE A SEAT, BRO .
SO HOW DO YOU TWOKNOW EACH OTHER?
OH, MICHAEL AND IWENT TO PENN TOGETHER.
SO YOU'VE KNOWN EACH OTHERFOR A LONG TIME?
THAT RIGHT.FELL OUT OF TOUCH A WHILE BACK,
BUT JUSTBUMPED INTO EACH OTHER AGAIN.
I GUESS EVERYBODY'SMOVING OUT HERE NOW.
YEAH, I GUESS SO.
HI, MR. BAKER.WHAT CAN I GET FOR YOU TODAY?
JUST THE USUAL, SWEETIE.OKAY.
YEAH, I'VE BEEN COMING HEREFOR A WHILE NOW.
MUST BE NICE TO BE IN THE KNOW.
IT IS. IT WASN'TALWAYS LIKE THIS, THOUGH.
FIRST TIME I CAME IN HERE,THIS PLACE WASA COMPLETE SHITHOLE.
NO ENGLISH ON THE MENU FORWESTERNERS, YOU KNOW THE DRILL.
TALKED TO THE OWNER,COMPLETELY STUBBORN ASSHOLEWOULDN'T CHANGE A THING.
BROUGHT INSOME BANKER FRIENDS,
THREW SOME ELBOWS,MADE SOME CHANGES.
TWO WEEKS LATER,EATING OUT OF MY HAND.CLASSIC M &amp; A.
NOW LOOK AT THE PLACE,MAKING LOTS OF MONEYOFF OUR PAYCHECKS, HUH?
YOU GOT IT.( laughs )
SO HOW DO YOU THINKTHE LOCALS FEEL ABOUTTHE CHANGES IN THE MENU?
LOCALS? WHO CARES?
I KNOW, ALL RIGHT?BUT JUST LOOSEN UP!
HE'S A REALLY GOOD GUY,AND IT'S GONNA BE A GOOD NIGHT.
SO JUST GIVE HIM A CHANCE,ALL RIGHT?
RED OR WHITE?RED.
MAN, YOU ARE GONNA LOVETHESE BITCHES I HAVE LINED UPFOR US TONIGHT.
HEY, LET MEASK YOU A QUESTION--
HEY, WHOA, WHOA, WHOA.
HOLD ON A SECOND, DON'T TELL METHAT YOU'RE FALLING
FOR THAT MYSTERY CHICKYOU'VE BEEN HANGING OUT WITH?
NO, NO--THERE ARE RULESHERE IN ASIA, BRO.
RULE NUMBER ONE:ALWAYS WEAR A CONDOM.
RULE NUMBER TWO:NEVER FALL IN LOVE.
HEY! YO!
YOU'RE A MILLION MILES AWAY.
WE'VE GOT BIG THINGSIN THE WORKS, BRO.
YOU ARE ON YOUR WAYTO THE MAJOR LEAGUES.
HOW'S THAT SOUND, HUH? HUH?
COME ON, LETS GO CELEBRATE.
HEY, IT'S THAT CHICKTHAT WORKS FOR FEI &amp; CHANG!
WHAT'S THAT SAY?UH...
"LOCAL GIRLWORKS HER WAY TO THE TOP BYSLEEPING WITH THE CEO'S SON."
WHAT A FUCKING SLUT!AH, MAN! PRICELESS!GET THAT SLUT OUT OF YOUR HEAD.
WHEN THIS IS OVERAND IT FALLS IN HER FACE,
SHE'S GONNA BE GOLD-DIGGINGHER WAY INTO THE NEXTCORPORATE FAMILY.
SO WHATARE YOU WORRIED ABOUT?
( speaking Cantonese )WHOA, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
WHAT, YOU THINK YOU'REACTUALLY HELPING THESE PEOPLEBY GIVING THEM CHANGE?
( speaking Cantonese )
LOOK, YOU CRIPPLEDHOMELESS FUCK.
GET THE FUCK AWAY FROM ME!
CHILL OUT!
SORRY, BRO. COME ON.LET'S GET OUT OF HERE.
( door buzzes )
Both: HEY!
SOMEBODY RING FOR A PARTY?
♪ AND I PUT MYSELFIN A HURRICANE ♪
♪ AND I CLEANSE MYSELFIN THE POURING RAIN ♪
♪ SHE STARES THROUGH YOUAND YOU FEEL A PULL ♪
♪ LIKE LIGHTNING IN THE NIGHTSO BEAUTIFUL ♪
♪ I TAKE MYSELFTO THE HURRICANE ♪
♪ AND I CLEANSE MYSELFOF ALL THE FEAR AND PAIN ♪
♪ SHE STARES THROUGH ME ♪
JUST DO IT.
♪ AND I FEEL A PULL ♪
♪ LIKE THE FIRE IN THE NIGHTSO BEAUTIFUL ♪
( laughs )
♪ TAKE ME DOWN... ♪
JUST REMEMBERWHO'S GOT YOUR BACK.
♪ ...AND FLY TO YOU ♪
♪ I NEED YOUIN THE MORNING LIGHT ♪
♪ IN THE EYE OF THE STORM ♪
( door buzzes )
GOOD MORNING.
I'M SORRY, WHO ARE--
NATALIE?
NATALIE!
NATALIE! NATALIE, WAIT!
HOW MUCH?HOW MUCH WAS IT WORTH TO YOU?
ARE YOU SERIOUS?I DIDN'T SLEEP WITH HER.
THEN WHAT SHEDOING UP THERE? HUH, WHAT?
SHE CAME TO STROKE YOUR EGO,YOU PIECE OF SHIT?!
WHAT ABOUT YOU AND RICHARD, HUH?WHAT?
YEAH, RICHARD!
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
COME ON, TABLOIDS!ARE YOU USING ME?
I DON'T KNOW WHAT KIND OF GAMEYOU'RE PLAYING!
ARE YOU SERIOUS, CONNER?
IS THAT WHAT YOU REALLY THINK?I DON'T KNOW WHATTO THINK ANYMORE!
OKAY, JUST ANSWERTHE FUCKING QUESTION!ARE YOU FUCKING HIM OR NOT?!
YEAH, YOU DON'T KNOWWHAT TO THINK
BECAUSE YOU'RE TOO BUSYFOLLOWING DIRECTIONS
AND JUST FOLLOWINGOTHER PEOPLE
THAT YOU DON'T HAVE TIMETO THINK FOR YOURSELF.
LOOK AT YOU.EVERYDAY YOU GO OUT THERE,YOU PLACE BETS, YOU TAKE RISKS,
BUT YOU CAN'T EVENTAKE A GAMBLE ON US!
YOU'RE SO SCARED, CONNER.
SO SCARED.
I THOUGHT YOU WEREBETTER THAN THAT.
YOU'RE NOT THE ONLY ONETAKING A RISK.
( dialing )
( speaking Cantonese )
A GRISLY SCENE TODAYAT THE FEI &amp; CHANG SHIPYARD,
WHERE THE BODY OF A MANHAS BEEN FOUND.
AT THIS STAGE,THERE ARE UNCONFIRMED REPORTS
THAT THE DEATHHAS BEEN A SUICIDE.
AND OF COURSE THIS ISTHE LATEST IN A STRING
OF VERY NEGATIVE PUBLICITYTO SURROUND THIS COMPANY
WHICH HAS BEEN EXPERIENCINGSEVERE FINANCIAL PROBLEMS.
MORE DETAILS SOON.
( siren wails in distance )
( camera shutters clicking )
SIR, A COMMENT, PLEASE.
( sighs )
I JUST HEARD THE NEWS.
TOUGH BREAK, BRO.
IT HAPPENSTO THE BEST OF US,
AND ALL WE CAN DOIS SHAKE IT OFF AND MOVE ONTO THE NEXT ONE.
THAT'S WHAT WE DO.
I THOUGHT SHE WAS DIFFERENT.
SHE? WHAT THE FUCKARE YOU TALKING ABOUT, BRO?
NATALIE.YOU HAVEN'T HEARD?
HEARD WHAT?
MR. CHAU, V.P. OF I.T.FOR FEI &amp; CHANG,
WAS FOUND DEAD THIS MORNING...
( sighs )
( dialing )
( beeps )
MICHAEL BAKER, PLEASE.
( crying )
ITS GONNA BE OKAY.
IT'S GONNA BE OKAY.( sniffles )
I PROMISEI'LL MAKE THIS RIGHT.
OKAY? ( sniffles )
( sighs )
( sniffles )
HEY, I'M...I'M SORRY.
IT'S ALL RIGHT.( sniffles )
WHAT HAPPENED?
NO ONE KNOWS.
THEY JUST FOUNDA PRINTED OUT SUICIDE NOTE.
NO WAY.
I'M GONNA BRING SOME TEAUP TO MRS. CHAU.
ALL RIGHT.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO LEAVE.
( chuckles )YOU TRICKED ME.
I THOUGHT YOU WERE SLEEPING.
YOU KNOW MY, UH...MY DADDY DIED, TOO.
REALLY?YEAH.
YOU'RE GONNA REMEMBER THIS DAYFOR THE REST OF YOUR LIFE.
( sighs )EVERY SINGLE DETAIL.
AND YOU KNOW, ONE DAY...
MAYBE NOT NOWOR TEN YEARS FROM NOW...
YOU'RE GONNA HATE HIM.
YOU'RE GONNA HATE HIMBECAUSE HE WASN'T THERE...
TO CHEER FOR YOU AT YOURCHAMPIONSHIP BASEBALL GAME,
OR HEAR YOU GIVE YOURVALEDICTORIAN SPEECH
AT YOURHIGH SCHOOL GRADUATION.
AND YOU'RE...
YOU'RE GONNA FEELLIKE ANYTHING YOU DO...
WON'T BE GOOD ENOUGH...
THAT ANYTHING YOU DO...
WON'T MATTER...
'CAUSE IT WON'T BRING HIM BACK.
AND ONE DAY...
YOU'LL UNDERSTAND.
HOLD ON TO THAT FOR ME.
COME ON, WE GOTTA GO.
EVERYTHING OKAY?
YEAH, FINE.
LISTEN UH, BUNCH OF US AREGATHERING FOR DRINKS DOWNSTAIRSIF YOU WANT TO JOIN.
UH, GOT A LOT OF WORK.I'LL TRY TO JOIN, THOUGH.
OKAY, BRO.
( door shuts )
( dialing )
YEAH, ANDY,I FOUND THE SHORT TRANSACTIONS,
BUT THEY'RE LOCKED.
FUCK! UH...
YOU'RE GONNA TO HAVE TO ACCESSTHEM ON QUENTIN'S COMPUTER.
OKAY.
( door opens )
BLOODY SECOND TIME THIS WEEK...
WHAT'S UP, CONNER?
UH, HEY, UM...
YOU KNOW,I LEFT MY NOTEBOOK IN THERE.
YOU WOULDN'T BY CHANCEKNOW QUENTIN'S CODE?
OH, YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.SURE, SURE.
I SAW HIM PUNCH IT INONCE FROM OVER THERE.
( both chuckle )
ALL RIGHT, LET ME REMEMBER...
( beeps )
BINGO. NOT VERY HARD, IS IT?
NOT AS IF IT'S 'SLUT'OR SOMETHING.
( both chuckle )
SERIOUSLY, MAN,HE'S GOT WEIRD TASTE IN ART.
SORRY, HAVE YOU FOUNDWHAT YOU'RE LOOKING FOR?
I CAN'T FIND IT,BUT, UM, THANKS ANYWAYS.
NO WORRIES.
SO YOU GONNA COME DOWNSTAIRSLATER ON AND HAVE A FEW BEVIESWITH THE LADS?
RIGHT, UH, YEAH, I HEARD.I GOT A LOT OF STUFF TO DO.
SO...I'LL TRY.
YOU OKAY, MATE?
YEAH, FINE.
ALL RIGHT, MATE.SEE YOU LATER, YEAH?YEAH.
DON'T WORK TOO HARD!OKAY.
( door opens and closes )
( beeps )
FUCK, THERE'S A LOGIN.
QUENTIN'S NOT THE BRIGHTEST.THINK LIKE HIM.
BARS, CHICKS, NUMBERS,INSIDE JOKES, WHATEVER.
ONE SECOND.
SLUT.
OKAY, I'M IN.COPYING IT RIGHT NOW.
HEY, MAN.
( beeps )
YOU COMING?
SORRY, WHAT?
I SAID, ARE YOU COMING?
YOU KNOW WHAT? UH...
YEAH, I DON'T THINKIT'S GONNA WORK OUT.I JUST GOT WAY TOO MUCH WORK.
IT'S NOT THE SAMEWITHOUT YOU, BRO.
YEAH, BUT YOU KNOW, I THINKIT'S GONNA BE AN ALL-NIGHTER.
YOU SURE?
POSITIVE, THANKS.
EVERYTHING'S ALL RIGHT?
YEAH, REALLY. NEXT TIME.
OKAY.
( door opens and closes )
( sighs )
( beeps )
OKAY, I THINKIT FINISHED COPYING.
FUCK, BUT THERE'S NO NAMES.
YOU'RE GONNA NEED SOMEBODYAT FEI &amp; CHANG
TO MATCHTHE TRANSACTION NUMBERS.
FUCK!
HEY, JAMES. HEY, BEAUTIFUL.
HEY! WHAT ARE YOU DOING, MATE?DON'T BE CRACKING ON MY BIRD!
CONNER FIND HIS NOTEBOOK?
WHAT NOTEBOOK?
HE SAID HE LEFT ITIN YOUR OFFICE.
( siren wails in distance )
YOU LUCK BOX.
GET OFF ME.
( chuckles ) LET HIM GO.
( sighs )
WE NEED TO TALK.
TALKING IS SO BLASé.BLAH BLAH BLAH.
YOU AMERICAN'S LOVE TO TALK.
LOOK, RICHARD--
NO, YOU LOOK.
YOU WANT TO STAY,THEN PUT YOUR BLOOD MONEYWHERE YOUR MOUTH IS.
FINE.
AH, NOW DOESN'T THATFEEL MUCH BETTER?
MONEY, WEALTH, FORTUNE.
CONNER, WHO CARES?
YOUR WESTERN PHILOSOPHY
IS THE ONE WITHTHE MOST TOYS WINS.
BUT CAN'T YOU SEE?
NOT THIS TIME, MR. AMERICA.NOT THIS TIME.
WE ALL LOSE!
I KNOW WE HAVEN'TSEEN EYE TO EYE,BUT I CAN HELP YOU.
I JUST NEEDTO MATCH THESE RECORDSWITH YOUR FINANCIAL DATA
TO GET EVIDENCE ON WHOIS MAKING SHORT TRADESON YOUR COMPANY.
AND WHY SHOULDI LISTEN TO YOU NOW?
SUDDENLY YOU CAREABOUT HELPING MY COMPANY?
I DON'T GIVE A SHITABOUT YOUR COMPANY.
MR. CHAU--DON'T YOU EVEN SAY HIS NAME!
MR. CHAU IS DEAD!DON'T YOU...EVEN SAY HIS NAME!
( breathing heavily )
ALL IN.
I FOLD.
FLIP IT.
YOU SURE YOU WANT TO DO THIS?
IF YOU'RE NOT GAMBLING,YOU'RE NOT LIVING.
( bang )
OKAY, I'M GONNA GOCHECK ON THIS REAL QUICK.
CONNER!
NO! NO!
I'M NOT GOING IN THE CLOSET!
FUCKERS! GET OVER HERE!
Richard:YOU'RE SO AMERICAN.
YOU'RE THE BLINDLEADING THE BLIND.
Donald: WHAT DO YOU KNOWABOUT FAMILY, MR. LEE?
Natalie: YOU'RE SO SCARED,CONNER. SO SCARED.
( grunting )
( groans )
NO! NO! NO! NO!( screams )
FOR THE LAST FIVE YEARS.WHAT ABOUT ASIA?
WE GOT A GUYSET UP IN HONG KONG.
REAL SMART.KNOWS HIS STUFF.
( phone vibrates )
THAT'S HIM RIGHT NOW.
YEAH?
WE CREATE EVENTS.
( groaning )
( continues groaning )
( chuckles )
( groaning )
YOU ALL RIGHT?
WHY? WHY?!
WHY WHAT?
YOU USED ME!
YEAH, I DID.
MICHAEL? HE'S BEEN PUSHING FORTHE POISON PILL THIS WHOLE TIME.
THEY'RE FINALLYGONNA GO THROUGH WITH IT.
THE STOCK PRICE WILL DROPAND OUR SHORT POSITIONS WILLFAR OUTDO YOUR BUY POSITIONS.
WE'RE GOING TO MAKE500 MILLION, GUARANTEED!
FIVE HUNDRED MILLION?FIVE HUNDRED FUCKING MILLION?!WHO FUCKING CARES?!
THIS IS NOT A GAME, QUENTIN!
OH, IT'S ALL A GAME!
AND YOU PLAYED IT LIKE A CHAMP!
ALL THOSE LETTER YOU WROTE?
THE AUDITORS, THE PRESS?
IT'S ALL PART OF IT.
COME ON, CONNER.
IT'S EASIER TO MAKEA STOCK PRICE GO DOWN
THAN MAKE IT GO UP,ISN'T IT?
AND BESIDES, WHO REALLY LOSES?
MR. CHAU? WAS HEA FUCKING NUMBER TO YOU?!
YEAH, THAT'S...
WHY'D YOU FUCKING DO IT, MAN?!EASY, BRO.
IF HIS OWN SIDEWANTS TO TAKE HIM OUT,I CAN'T HELP THAT.
THAT'S RIGHT.CHECK YOUR FACTS.
MARK WOULD NEVERLET THIS FUCKING HAPPEN!
MARK?YEAH, MARK!
IT WAS HIS IDEA TO SEND YOUOUT HERE IN THE FIRST PLACE.
OH, YOU THOUGHTYOU HAD FRIENDS?
YOU AIN'T GOTNO MOTHERFUCKING FRIENDS.
I WAS YOUR FRIEND!
YOU GOT MY BACK, RIGHT, BRO?HUH? YOU CHICKEN SHIT!
YOU PIECE OF SHIT!COME ON! COME ON!
( groans )OH! OUCH!
THAT MUST HAVE HURT, HUH?
YOU WANT A PIECE, CONNER?THAT'S RIGHT.
( grunts )MISSED!
( grunts )BOO YA!
( groans )
IN WHAT WORLDWERE YOU LIVING IN
THAT YOU THOUGHTYOU COULD BEAT ME? ME!
LOOK AT ME.
THIS IS MY CITY!
( grunting )
( chuckles )
( groans )
YOU WERE SUPPOSED TO BE MY BOY.
INSTEAD YOU END UPBEING MY BITCH!
HEY, QUENTIN...
DIU LE LO MO!
NO, YOU'RE THE ONETHAT'S FUCKED.
OH, WELL, LOOK,YOUR BOYFRIENDCAME TO RESCUE YOU.
( groans )
ENOUGH!
HEY, RICH, WHAT UP YO?
COME TO RESCUETHIS PRETTY PIECE OF ASS?
WELL, I TELL YOU WHAT,YOU CAN HAVE IT
AFTER I FINISHKICKING THE SHIT OUT OF IT.
UNTIL THEN, IT'S NONEOF YOUR FUCKING BUSINESS.
INTERESTING USE OF WORDS.
IT'S THE ONE THING THATYOU HAVEN'T LEARNED, QUENTIN...
THAT THERE ARE SOME THINGSTHAT ARE MORE IMPORTANTTHAN BUSINESS.
YEAH? AND WHAT'S THAT,YOU ASS FUCKER?
LIKE LOYALTY.
( speaking Cantonese )
( groans )
ARE YOU OKAY?
YOU REALLY ARE A DUMB AMERICAN.
( grunting )
( groans )
Michael: SO, I JUST NEED YOUTO SIGN HERE...
RIGHT HERE...
AND FINALLY RIGHT HERE.
( phone vibrates )
YEAH?
LET ME TALK TO DONALD.
OH, UH...DONALD IS BUSY.
FUCK.
WHO WAS THAT?
EH...GO ON.
ALL RIGHT, SO FINALLY HERE,
AND RIGHT HERE AS WELL.
DON'T SIGN THOSE DOCUMENTS!
WHAT'S GOING ON? RICHARD!
RICHARD WAS WORKING ONA COMPUTER SYSTEM,
ONE THAT WOULDREVOLUTIONIZE THE INDUSTRYAND SAVE YOUR COMPANY.
THIS IS LUDICROUS!IS IT, MICHAEL?
YOU GUYS KNOW EACH OTHER?
MR. CHAUWAS DESIGNING THE SYSTEM.
RICHARD AND I HAVE BEEN WORKINGON A WAY TO PRESENT THIS TO YOU,MR. CHANG.
OH, I'VE HEARD ENOUGH!
OH, IT GETS BETTER.
INTRODUCING THE FEI &amp; CHANGINTERNAL SOCIAL NETWORK.
SEE, EACH EMPLOYEEGETS THEIR OWN ACCOUNT,
ONE WHERE THEY CANNOT ONLY
KEEP TABS ON ONE ANOTHER,SHARE WORK ITEMS,
BUT GETS DAILY POINTSFOR THE GOOD WORKTHAT THEY'VE DONE.
AND AT THE END OF EACH QUARTERTHEY CAN TRADE IN THOSE POINTSFOR GIFTS,
OR GAMBLE IT AWAYFOR EVEN HIGHER REWARDS.
ONLY A VIDEO GAME.MAKES NO SENSE.
NO SENSE TO SOMEONEWHO'S NEXT IN LINE TO BE CEO.
SEE, THAT WASTHE PIECE OF THE PUZZLETHAT I DIDN'T UNDERSTAND--
HOW MICHAEL AND QUENTINWERE GOING TO CONVINCE YOUTO TAKE THE POISON PILL.
AND IT TOOK RICHARD HERETELLING ME HOW MUCH
OF AN AMERICAN I AMFOR ME TO REALIZE.
SEE, I TAKE EVERYTHINGAT FACE VALUE, BELIEVEWHATEVER I'M FED.
MARK SAW THAT IN MEAND THAT'S WHY HESENT ME OUT HERE.
YOU ARE DOING EXACTLYWHAT YOU SHOULD BE DOING.
TO SHAKE IT UP A LITTLE.
HE THOUGHT I COULD BE BOUGHT.
SO, SHORT POSITIONS,
FROM INSIDE FEI &amp; CHANGFROM OFFSHORE ACCOUNTS--
ACCOUNTS THAT ARELINKED TO VICTOR.
QUENTIN TOLD US EVERYTHING.
THIS IS OUTRAGEOUS!
WHY'D YOU KILLMR. CHAU, VICTOR?
WAS IT BECAUSEHE WAS BUILDING THE SYSTEMTHAT WOULD EXPOSE YOU? HMM?
MAYBE IT WAS BECAUSEYOU FINALLY REALIZEDYOU WOULD NEVER BECOME CEO.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
AND I THOUGHT YOU WEREALL ABOUT FAMILY, VICTOR.
I CAN'T STAND THIS!
WHY'D YOU KILLMR. CHAU, VICTOR?
WHY'D YOU KILLMR. CHAU, VICTOR?NO.
WHY DID YOU KILL HIM?HUH? HE HAD A SON!
WHY DID YOU KILL MR. CHAU?!WHY DID YOU KILL HIM, HUH?!
I DID IT FOR THE FAMILY!
THE COMPANY WAS BEINGRUN DOWN TO THE GROUND.
YOU THINK A LITTLE COMPUTER GAMEWAS GOING TO SOLVE OUR PROBLEMS?
NO!
THIS COMPANYNEEDS REAL LEADERSHIP!
I LOVEWHAT FATHER LEFT TO US
TOO MUCH TO SEE IT FAIL!
I DID IT--I DID IT FOR THE FAMILY.I DID IT FOR THE FAMILY!
( sobbing )
I...
( sighs )
NATALIE, CAN YOU--
I'M ON IT, MR. CHANG.
THANK YOU.
SO, CONNER, LOOKS LIKE YOU KNOWMY COMPANY BETTER THAN I DO.
IS THERE ANYTHING ELSEI SHOULD KNOW ABOUT?
IT'S ALL RIGHT, SON.YOU DON'T HAVE TO SAY ANYTHING.
I SHOULD HAVENEVER DOUBTED YOU.
( sighs )
( dialing )
( beeps )
HEY, CONNER.
SURPRISED TO HEAR FROM ME?
WELL, I ALWAYS SAIDYOU HAD YOUR FATHER'S EDGE.
IT'S OVER.
OH, NO, IT'S NOT OVER, KID.
IT'S JUST POSTPONED.
I KNOW ABOUT YOUR POSITIONSIN FEI &amp; CHANG.
I KNOW THAT YOU WERETHE ONE TO SET ME UP.
OH, YOU'RE DAMN RIGHTI WAS SETTING YOU UP!
I WAS SETTING YOU UPFOR THE REST OF YOUR LIFE,YOU UNGRATEFUL SHIT!
I WAS GONNA BRING YOU IN!
I WAS GIVING YOU EVERYTHING!
YOU GAVE ME NOTHINGAND NOW YOU'VE LOST IT ALL.
I BUILT THIS FUND FROM NOTHING,I'LL DO IT AGAIN.
YOU WANNA BET?
THE SFC ARE INVESTIGATING.
QUENTIN AND VICTOR--CONFESSING.
MARK, YOU'RE FINISHED.
I GUESS I BECAME THE MANI WAS SUPPOSED TO BE AFTER ALL.
( sighs )
ARE YOU READY TO GO?
JUST ONE MORE CALL TO MAKE.
HEY, MOM? YEAH, IT'S ME...
♪ AND I PUT MYSELFIN A HURRICANE ♪
♪ AND I CLEANSE MYSELFIN THE POURING RAIN ♪
♪ SHE STARES THROUGH YOU ♪
♪ AND YOU FEEL A PULL ♪
♪ LIKE LIGHTNING IN THE NIGHT ♪
♪ SO BEAUTIFUL ♪
♪ I TAKE MYSELFTO THE HURRICANE ♪
♪ AND I CLEANSE MYSELFOF ALL THE FEAR AND PAIN ♪
♪ SHE STARES THROUGH MEAND I FEEL A PULL ♪
♪ LIKE THE FIRE IN THE NIGHTSO BEAUTIFUL ♪
♪ TAKE ME DOWN,I NEED YOUR POWER ♪
♪ I LIFT MY ARMSAND FLY TO YOU ♪
♪ I NEED YOUIN THE MORNING ♪
♪ I NEED YOU ALL NIGHT ♪
♪ I NEED YOUIN THE MORNING LIGHT ♪
♪ IN THE EYE OF THE STORM ♪
♪ AND I STEAL MYSELFTO THE EYE OF THE STORM ♪
♪ THE COVER FALLSLIKE A NEW DAY'S DAWN ♪
♪ AND SHE SMILES AT MEAS I FEEL A PULL ♪
♪ LIKE A FIRE IN THE NIGHTSO BEAUTIFUL ♪
♪ I WILL HOLD YOU,KEEP YOU SAFE ♪
♪ OH, TILL THE HURRICANEIS GONE NOW ♪
♪ TILL THE HURRICANEIS GONE NOW, BABY ♪
♪ I WILL HOLD YOU,KEEP YOU SAFE ♪
♪ OH, TILL THE HURRICANEIS GONE NOW, BABY ♪
♪ TILL THE HURRICANEIS GONE NOW, GONE NOW ♪
♪ I WILL HOLD YOU,KEEP YOU SAFE ♪
♪ OH, TILL THE HURRICANEIS GONE NOW, BABY ♪
♪ TILL THE HURRICANEIS GONE NOW, GONE NOW ♪
♪ I WILL HOLD YOU,KEEP YOU SAFE ♪
♪ IT'S THE EYE OF THE STORM ♪